Raymond Alake

London, SE16 2BU

Contacts: 07732395796 | ralake95@gmail.com

Profiles: www.linkedin.com | github.com

An exceptionally creative and dependable Junior Front End Web developer with two years of experience in designing and developing modern Web platforms. A highly adaptable professional who embraces teamwork, but also enjoys working independently. Proficient in current JavaScript framework and libraries, alongside toolset of design applications.

EXPERIENCE

Hiveli

Front End Web Developer June 2016 - Aug 2018, London

- Aided the development of a dynamic secure website from the foundation.
- Produced a versatile style-guide ensuring a consistent vibrant theme across pages.
- Accomplished an active line of communication with backend developers guaranteeing a systematic workflow.
- Adhered to compatibility and accessibility traditions.

MoChunks

Front End Web Developer Aug 2017 - Oct 2017, London

- Led the design and development and successfully created a visually appealing, userfriendly interface with interactive features optimising site traffic.
- Collaborated with the client to outline project requirements and timeline.
- Provided ongoing maintenance for the production site.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, Angular, TypeScript, ES6, Angular Material, Bootstrap, BEM, Git, GitHub, Chrome Developer Tools, UI, UX, Affinity Designer.

Portfolio: raymondalake.co.uk

- Project management with Trello.
- · High verbal and written skills.
- Profoundly creative and analytical problemsolver.

EDUCATION

Lancaster University

Economics BSc Hons: Sep 2014 to 2018.

PROJECTS

Circlearn

August 2018

A time management tool, helping university students remain on top of work, grades and social life.

INTERESTS

When not coding, studying or pushing pixels, you can find me working out at the gym or catching some much-needed rest.